From the previous episode...
Mash was pretty good at tennis as well.
And was merciless.
Divine Visionary Candidate Exam,
qualifying round...
"The Life Crystal" still continues.
I hear a "Re."
You see, power and pitch
fuse together in my head.
Your power is a "Re" in the
"Do-Re-Mi-Fa-Sol-La-Ti-Do" scale.
The higher your pitch, the stronger you are.
You two are at the second tier
from the bottom.
The likes of you will never
show me the coming of spring.
Quickly put your crystals down
and begone from here.
You know it's two-on-one, right?
You're not in a position to be able to say...
...this and that!
Wulfes!
Roks!
I am fully aware that Macaron
is as powerful as a Divine Visionary.
But both of us have gathered
three gold coins each to be here.
We're in the top tier, too.
We can't lose two-on-one...
Sounds: Ray, A Drop of Golden Sun!
- Wulf Shield!
- Rok Shield!
Two-on-one, and with one basic spell...
How can a fellow student be so...
...so much more powerful?
Damn it, my body won't move...
My pitch is "Ti" on that scale.
You two are "Re" put together.
I hope the difference between us is clear.
Th-They're too strong!
That's enough!
One team dropped out,
so the exam is over!
It ended before I could do anything.
Oh well. In any case, we got through!
We're moving on!
HUP HUP HUP
Go, go, Mushroom!
Push, push, Mushroom!
A word from today's MVP,
Mash Burnedead.
How was the qualifying round?
I want a cream puff.
That's not an answer at all!
The end! Hurray!
It's suddenly quiet.
Mash Burnedead.
The greatest trial for you begins here.
Finally, we can see them get serious.
The only one who gave Rayne Ames
a run for his money last year...
Margarette Macaron's true strength.
The ripening summer... is here.
I'll look forward to the next exam, Mash.
What's wrong, Mash?
TWITCH TWITCH
Mike told me to be careful.
Mike? Oh, you mean your pecs.
Facing someone like Macaron makes it
difficult for Mushroom Head to move on.
Right, Mr. Wahlberg?
The reason why Rayne Ames was able
to become Divine Visionary as a second-year
was largely due to the fact that
Macaron didn't participate in the exam.
As the head of Magic Talent Administration,
I carefully examine every candidate each year.
And in my opinion, the surest candidate
for Divine Visionary
is Margarette Macaron.
I witnessed in person Macaron devastating
that tournament a few years ago.
Especially their Secondth is...
Indeed.
Sorry. I couldn't help it.
I'm sure you'd like to say,
"that's only under normal circumstances."
You really do take his side quite a bit.
I have no idea what makes him so alluring.
Macaron has the qualifications
to become Divine Visionary.
And I doubt that Mushroom Head
has that much aptitude.
That's just how overwhelming
the difference between them is.
That kid embarrassed me
during the qualifying round.
I'm gonna make sure
that Mushroom Head goes down.
Macaron, they say Mushroom Head
can't use magic.
Please beat him up
on behalf of us magic users.
I wouldn't mind slipping
a laxative in his...
Please don't do anything
do dampen my fun.
I'll kill you.
You hear?
That goes for even you...
Orter Madl.
I'll stay quiet
as long as you get the job done.
I see.
Holding their own against a Divine Visionary...
So this is Margarette Macaron!
Why do I train so hard?
It all began when Pops told me to.
At first, it felt heavy and was so tiring...
I really hated it.
But as I begrudgingly kept doing it,
I could hold more and more weight.
Nowadays, I can hold
my head up high and say it.
The reason why I pump iron...
That's because...
There's a dumbbell there, I guess?
Do you know why humans have arms?
It's so they can hold dumbbells.
Do you know why humans have legs?
It's so we can deadlift barbells.
Nobody's asking,
but he started talking on his own.
Do you know why humans have heads—
Why do I continue
to be an emotional burden?
And here comes the second one!
At first I wasn't
an emotional burden at all.
But gradually, I started swaying between
joy and sorrow with each of his moves.
So if there's a reason why I continue
to be an emotional burden...
it would be because...
the one I love is right there, I guess?
What is with this useless flow of time?
The emotional burden comes from love.
I'm not good enough to be your partner?
No way!
I wanna go home.
Please, can I somehow?
Never!
I got rejected!
PSSSH
It's this late already?
I have to drink my protein.
Everyone is in their own world.
Providing nutrition to the muscles
is great training in itself.
Impressive.
That is a noble undertaking.
I'd like to follow suit.
When did he...
Oh, the Divine Visionary
who bullied me the other day.
He means this guy.
What is a Divine Visionary doing here?
You've caught my interest.
Want to play a little game?
You've got time before the next round.
No way.
I want to get some rest.
He refused!
He just sassed that Divine Visionary.
You really are gonna go far.
I'm the head
of Magic Talent Administration.
Anyone joining the Bureau of Magic
always get adjudicated by me.
Unless I acknowledge you, you may not
be able to become a Divine Visionary.
Oh, there's nothing we can do.
I'm the head of Magic Talent,
but there's nothing I can do.
I'll do it.
He's suddenly so interested!
Well, I feel sorry for you
to play a game for nothing.
If you can beat me, I'll grant you
a pass on this exam, no questions asked.
Pass the exam? Good for you, Mash.
By the way, what will we play?
Oh, it's a simple game.
"You look, you lose."
"You look, you lose"?
I couldn't ask for more.
I accept your challenge.
His fingers are moving so quickly
it looks like a flower.
Mash agreed to play "You look, you lose"
against Kaldo,
a Divine Visionary
who suddenly appeared.
A circle?
Of course, it's a slight variation
of "You look, you lose."
There will be no rock-paper-scissors.
Furthermore, I will point my finger first.
After I count down from three,
you win if you stayed in that circle
and not face the way I'm pointing.
With those rules, Mash would have
overwhelming advantage.
What's the catch?
BRING IT ON
Gotcha.
We'll do three rounds.
If you dodge in all three rounds, you win.
'Kay.
Well then, here goes.
You look, you lose.
Three.
What? An attack from the ground!?
Two.
It wasn't an ordinary game after all!
One.
He's using magic to force him to look up.
Zero.
Close one.
Oh, nice move.
Let's keep going.
You look, you lose.
What? Two directions?
Three.
Now, he has to either look left or right...
Two.
...or he can't dodge that!
One.
Zero.
You can just manage stuff like this
with your bare hands, huh?
How quaint.
How very quaint.
Black flames from his sword...
The black flame enchanting this sword keeps
burning whatever it touches until it burns out.
Which means, this makes it impossible
to take the hit like you did earlier.
HONK
Scary.
No, Mash! This is too dangerous!
It's better if you stop!
I wanna stop.
Well, this is the last one. Here goes.
You look, you lose.
What? Three directions?
He loses unless he looks down.
Three.
Two.
...close.
One.
The instant he looks down,
a sword swings up from below.
He can't look down like this!
He scooped out the entire circle
on the ground before jumping...
...to dodge that while still looking down!
Oh, I looked right.
I lost.
No, we won't count that one.
I'll say this challenge was a draw.
Is that okay with you?
Well, if you don't mind...
But at your current level, it might be
difficult to go up against Macaron.
Sorry to have bothered you.
Man, that sent a chill down my spine.
What's wrong, Mash?
Oh, I would have been in danger
if he didn't hesitate for a moment.
Besides...
He didn't cast any spells.
Mushroom Head.
He tried to take the blow of my sword
with his forehead at first.
He's off the rails.
What's the reason that he needs
to be a Divine Visionary that badly?
Everything is for naught if you die.
But, if he were to be on our side...
Come on up to our level.
After a short break, the time has finally come.
We will now begin the final exam!
The final exam is a one-on-one battle!
The rules are simple.
You win if your opponent
gives up or passes out.
Let's start the first matchup!
Adler dorm first-year.
With seven gold coins,
the most out of any candidate...
Mash Burnedead!
Opposing him is Orca dorm,
who acquired five coins...
Margarette Macaron!
Go for it, Mash.
For your future...
and the future of your grandpa.
Even in Easton's storied history,
Margarette Macaron's talents are a rarity.
This is your greatest crisis,
Mash Burnedead.
I'm terribly sorry, but you won't
be able to go any further.
You should fulfill your destiny
of amusing me...
Mash Burnedead.
That's quite absurd.
Now, for our first match...
Oh, hold on a sec.
I need to replenish calories
before my workout.
My, what a coincidence.
Mind if I join you?
Dip! Dip! Dip! Dip! Dip!
Dip! Deep! Dip! Deep!
Dip! Dip!
If you put that much tartare sauce on it,
you won't know
what the fried shrimp tastes like.
What are you talking about?
I'm putting fried shrimp on my tartare sauce.
Fried shrimp exists to eat tartare sauce
in a more tasty way.
HONK
Those are the eyes of a madman.
I sense a formidable opponent.
Wicked.
Based on my completely biased reasoning,
the crazier someone is,
the more powerful they are.
That means this is a real badass.
The reason why Orter chose Macaron
is because of the certainty.
He didn't do anything between
the first attack and this tournament
because he has faith
in Macaron's abilities.
Which means he believes that Macaron
surely is able to finish Mash Burnedead.
That's how obvious the difference
in skill between them is.
Well then, here goes.
A-Amazing.
What magical power...
I feel ill.
You okay?
It's no surprise you're affected.
There's that much magical power.
This is the power said to be
equal to Divine Visionaries.
Try overcoming this, Mash Burnedead.
Nalcos.
What? That's just basic magic.
What's going on?
Mash can easily deal with...
It's heavy like a bowling ball.
What the... Mash can't return the serve!
He'll hit the wall!
Mash!
Surely this isn't the end?
He's gone.
Where did he go?
Spine Magic...
Hell Fall!!
Brutal.
He slammed them down.
That's gotta be game right there.
One shot against Macaron.
How did Mash escape that attack earlier?
I thought he hit the wall.
He was running backwards.
Mash decided that he couldn't
return the magic serve,
and ran backwards faster than the spell
to escape before he slammed against the wall.
Wha? Freaky.
But you know, all this about
bowling and returning serves.
The vocabulary just doesn't sound
like a magic school.
Oh well, whatever.
Look!
H-He's unhurt! How in the world...
It's just beginning.
I'm far from having enough enjoyment.
Isn't that right...
Mash Burnedead?
NEXT EPISODE
MASH BURNEDEAD AND THE MAGICAL MAESTRO