I've been looking for you,
Mash Burnedead.
Oh, how beautiful.
I didn't think I'd find you alive.
I felt despair thinking
I would never obtain you.
My dear, sweet...
...son.
By incorporating you into me,
I will become complete.
Now, shall we?
You shall not.
I cannot simply hand that child
over to you...
Innocent Zero.
Wahlberg.
As the headmaster of Easton,
I cannot overlook any further disorder.
And I certainly will not let you
meddle with our students.
Even if it kills me.
Gotta hand it to Wahlberg.
He doesn't bat an eye
at time-stopping magic.
But him showing up was all expected.
We will take our credit.
Wh-What was that just now?
Bloodthirst?
You're trembling from fear.
Back off, you insignificant speck!
Don't bully my dear allies
so much, Wahlberg.
Poor things.
What is your true objective?
Objective.
I only wish to become a perfect human.
Undying, beautiful, and powerful.
That's all I want.
How commonplace.
You would sacrifice countless lives for that?
Stealing magical power,
tormenting, and even killing...
Where's the problem?
Don't ask about the obvious, Wahlberg.
My family exists for my sake.
Even Mash Burnedead over there.
He exists for my sake. He is mine.
He is my son.
Of course I will take him with me.
Back to our home.
Indeed, we are destined to be
truly incompatible.
Mash Burnedead will become
the beacon of hope for this world.
If you want to take him no matter the cost,
then you will have to go through me.
It's been decades...
since we crossed wands.
Summon Uranus!
Summon Chronos!
I have no need of anyone
but Mash Burnedead.
I shall dispose of all of you now.
What the hell is going on?
I will explain everything later.
Those who can move,
deal with the demons.
I will deal with Innocent Zero.
I trust you with the students.
Sounds Fa!
Explomb!
Graviole!
What are these things?
I get that we're in a terrible situation,
and I know that
we're in terrible danger.
Innocent Zero.
I must hurry to assist Mr. Wahlberg.
So tough.
Then...
Each and every one of them
has enough power to be a double-liner.
Orter.
Kaldo, head over
as backup for Mr. Wahlberg.
Looks like they don't
want us over there.
Why're there so many?
Quit your whining and get to work!
Sounds Re!
Is it all right to leave it
in the hands of a few students?
Why don't you worry about yourself?
Here, we will not be interrupted.
There's no end in sight.
We'll get support in time.
We have to hold out until...
Wait, that guy...
That thing...
Trying to drop that on us?
Not good!
They have someone
to keep every one of us busy.
ALONE...
But none are going after
sweet little Mash.
He's being baited.
This is a trap.
I expect they possess a surefire way
to get sweet little Mash.
Seriously? How'd you figure that?
Just a woman's hunch.
So they have a woman's heart.
I was wondering about that the whole time.
Mash! You can leave this place
to us for now!
You're the only one who can pummel
Innocent Zero's heavy hitter in that tower! For real!
'Kay!
Such a big tower would take
too much time to climb.
And he'd become an easy target
for the enemy.
Playing Daruma drop
with the tower. Cool.
We meet again, Mash Burnedead.
It's useless to topple the tower.
That magic won't disappear
unless you defeat me...
U-Um... Been a while since... you sat
next to me in the entrance ceremony?
Wait, have you forgotten about me?
I'm sorry.
Explomb!
Graviole!
Sounds Re!
There's no end to this!
Why is a baby...
Baebiez!
WHAT THE HELL!?
I am one of the Criminal Canes...
Sitter Baby.
My magic turns the targets into infants.
Infants are the materialization
of the word "inexperienced."
You will die without being able
to do anything.
WHAT WAS THAT?
I'LL GET YOU
WITH MY MAGIC!
EXPLOMB!
FIZZLE
CRAP!
Terrible. This is terrible.
I can't unleash any real magic.
I'm seriously going to die.
Damn it! I don't like it, but I have
to ask Lance for help.
There he is!
LANCE!
HELP ME!
Are you joking around? Just look at
what's happening around you.
What? I can't understand
a word of that.
Baebiez!
What? Magic?
So it was magic
that turned him into a baby?
Not that it matters,
but what a shameless look on his face.
It makes me so irritated.
Graviole!
I have to protect Dot in baby form
while I deal with these guys.
Graviole!
What are you doing?
WAIT! I'M ON MY WAY TO FULLY
RETURNING TO A BABY!?
Damn it!
Baebiez!
CRAP!
SHUT UP.
I CAN'T UNDERSTAND YOU!
I can tell that he's pissed off at me.
SHUT UP.
DAMN IT. MY BODY IS UNKNOWINGLY
REACTING TO THE TOY.
HMPH. I STILL HAVE A WAYS TO GO
IF I CAN'T CONTROL MYSELF...
The moment you turned into those forms,
your defeat was assured.
You can't use even a tenth
of your usual magical power.
How fun it is to have a one-sided
bullying of powerless creatures.
I have no worries of getting
injured myself. Truly one-sided.
Crap. At this rate, we really will be...
Now go.
CRAP!!
SECTIONAL GRAVIOLE.
What is going on?
This powerful even as an infant...
Impossible.
This guy...
His powers are limited, but he made up
for it by limiting the range of his magic.
The enemy's magic was powerful.
But the main caster was weak.
Still, so overwhelming.
This is the top of our class,
the genius, Lance Crown.
INDEED, THAT WAS ONE-SIDED, SCUM.
I don't know what the heck
he's saying, though.
Occasionally, you see someone in this world
that overcomes the age gap.
I wouldn't expect less from Easton.
We still have enemies.
Don't let your guard down.
I know that.
Mr. Ryoh.
What kind of relationship do Mr. Wahlberg
and Innocent Zero have?
This Magic Realm was shaped
by one great magic user.
He became the foundation
of Divine Visionaries.
Literally an individual
with power matching that of God.
His name was Adam.
In life, there was none who could
stand up to his dark magic.
Mr. Wahlberg and Innocent Zero
were Adam's best students.
So their powers are basically equal?
Right. But they made an effort
to invade us.
I'm sure they have some chance of success.
If Mr. Wahlberg were to lose
for any reason...
This is our first meeting in a while.
I feel happy about this.
My word.
That's pretty horrible.
You look upon your old friend
like I'm some kind of monster.
Or is it rather that...
You'll call me your friend
if I look like this?
Damn you, have you abandoned
your humanity?
I am more human than anyone.
I am too human,
and so my desires are too deep.
There's no limit to my greed.
I have two desires for today.
One is to take home my son,
Mash Burnedead.
The other is you, Wahlberg.
I want to make sure that you're dead.
Timez. The Living Dead.
This is...
a forbidden spell.
Are you serious?
You forgot who I am?
MASH'S POINT OF VIEW
Hey, are you listening, damn it!?
Kill. I'll kill you!
Looks like you finally remembered.
By the way, I heard.
Your friend was skewered
but is still alive.
They really are persistent like cockroaches.
After I'm done with you,
I'll go kill them with my own hands.
Your eyes are defiant.
Do you want to be skewered
like all your buddies?
Carborain!
I sure hope Mash is doing okay.
The overwhelming density
of that carbon lance.
Last time, he dealt with it
by going inside one of Abel's dolls.
But this time...
Hup hup hup!
He's running.
He's running on top of my magic.
Carborain!
Hup hup hup!
Carbo Heavy Rain!
Wh-Why?
Last time, all he could manage
was to avoid my attacks.
Yet, why...
I remember now.
You're the black thorny guy.
But I've seen it once before.
So, the same thing twice? Please.
NEXT EPISODE
WAHLBERG BAIGAN AND THE MAGIC OF DARKNESS