Headmaster Wahlberg is forced
into a tough battle against Innocent Zero,
but he uses the ultimate magic Spaces Thirds
to quickly turn the tide of battle.
Uranus Inclination!
Uranus World Delete!
The spatial magic unleashed with his life
on the line seemed to engulf Innocent Zero.
However, Innocent Zero rewound time
to nullify the magic.
Wahlberg had fallen
into a desperate crisis...
and what saved him was none other
than Mash's knee strike.
Mash Burnedead!
If I were to face something
that overwhelmingly outpowers me,
what would I do?
I'd knock the stuffing out of it...
with my fist!
Mash, you're so awesome.
But those legs are a bit... Yeah.
What's going on here, Kaldo?
The spatial magic that had been
deployed is all gone.
There's only one thing that I can think of.
Time magic rewound some time.
Time magic?
Innocent Zero, huh?
Kaldo, I'm leaving you in charge of here.
Understood.
Please take care of Mr. Wahlberg.
Who are you talking to?
This is me, after all!
That said, thinking about the situation,
I'm sure I'll have a hard time.
Please be safe for now, Mr. Wahlberg.
What are you doing, Mash Burnedead!?
This man is after you!
You must go immedi—
I was raised to be kind to the elderly.
You're saying that you'll treat me
just like any old man out there?
As I'd expect from Mash Burnedead.
I'm glad you came
all the way out here to see me.
My son.
Now, you shall come with me.
Wha...
Come.
I see. Then I will
have to take you by force.
But before that...
This is...
Headmaster!
With repeated
physical reconfiguration of my body,
I became able to steal
others' magical abilities.
Of course, I obtained
our master's dark magic as well.
And now Wahlberg,
your spatial magic is next.
Too late.
I-It can't be...
Oh yes it can.
Space Sacrifice.
This can't be... My magic...
Not only that,
but such a difference
in magical capacity...
Darn.
I gained the power to rule this world.
The world is mine now.
Mash Burnedead. You're next.
You will be mine.
No. If he gets Mash as well,
our hopes...
Doesn't faze me one bit.
I said it doesn't faze me.
That was close.
You felt the overwhelming difference
in power with your own body.
I will take you home with me,
Mash Burnedead.
What now?
His magical power is running
beyond his physical capacity.
That's the price of greedily seeking power.
I only wish to become a perfect human.
Undying, beautiful, and powerful.
That's all I want.
A perfect human.
To obtain a physical body
that can hold all magical power.
That's why he's after Mash Burnedead.
Don't get too cocky.
You are nothing more
than one of my ingredients.
Your only purpose in life is to elevate me
into a higher state of being.
That's simply your ego talking.
He has the right to decide
the course of his own life.
HONK
Totally that.
The course of his own life?
Humans like you who cannot use magic
can't live within this realm, anyway.
Shock!
Adam Jobs had ruled over
the Magic Realm for a long time.
He kept saying
Noblesse Oblige and the like,
but in the end, he could not stop the exclusion
for those who couldn't use magic.
Can't I say the same for you?
Right, Wahlberg?
Oh no.
With almost no magical power left,
I can't completely dodge it.
I didn't think he could still move this much.
But it doesn't change the fact that
we're in a very desperate situation.
With this much
power differential between us...
What a convenient tale, isn't it?
In a world where magic is everything,
the best magic user is such a despicable guy.
He's so worth defeating
with my muscles.
Then the world will accept me.
Ignorance can be such a scary thing.
It seems you cannot comprehend me,
an omnipotent being.
However, it seems I do require some time
to acclimate to this body as well.
Now if you'll excuse me.
That easily...
We'll finish this another time.
What is this magic?
The demons are disappearing.
It's useless to transfer
all the ones we've defeated.
They're right.
But this is Innocent Zero we're facing.
There has to be some reason...
I-It's gotten huge!
He fused together the corpses of the demons
we defeated to create a giant monster.
What is that?
That's...
You sure have quite a big mouth.
So stop it if you can, Mash Burnedead.
If someone without magic
is even capable of such a feat.
A monster in that state has enough power
to destroy an entire town instantly.
He decided to fight power with power,
and an overwhelming one.
O-Oh no, my magical power...
In the end, I make it just in time
during a crisis. That's who I am.
Ryoh.
Mr. Wahlberg! Those injuries...
We must take you to
the Bureau of Magic Hospital—
B-Be careful, Mash... Burne...
Mash?
Mushroom Head was here?
Oh, then I'll go look for him.
Sheesh. You promised me
you'll let me know when you find him.
However...
This was quite some hot stuff you did here.
You sure have quite a big mouth.
So stop it if you can, Mash Burnedead.
If someone without magic
is even capable of such a feat.
H-Huh?
What? What happened?
I feel like I was sleeping the whole time.
What in the world...
Huh? Where's the dragon?
Dot? Lance?
The time stoppage magic is gone.
That's not good.
People are going to panic.
No doubt.
I mean,
we have that monster over there.
What is that thing?
Is that a monster?
You're kidding me!
Hey, it's headed our way!
Is it trying to destroy our school!?
Lord Abel, that is...
Innocent Zero.
Mash.
Th-The rubble...
No!
Help me, big brother!
Graviole!
What? They stopped!
You always give me power, Anna.
What was that cutscene just now?
Did I just see one of your fantasies? Me?
Freaky!
Sounds Re!
Hurry! Get out of here!
We can't win against a monster like that.
Mash! Where are you, Mash!?
No matter how big this thing is...
Explomb!
It totally pulled that barrier thingy
out of nowhere.
What's up with that?
That's a magic-nullifying barrier.
Barrier?
You mean, just like the thing
that protected that thorny dude.
Yes. One of Innocent Zero's casters who put
that up should be around here somewhere.
If we don't defeat them,
magic won't work against that thing.
Orter is after the caster right now,
but I'm sure they're deftly hiding.
We can't do anything at present,
so I'm going to join the investigation.
M-Me too!
Hey, don't push! Help!
A monster that magic
doesn't work against? It's all over!
No good. There's a barrier
over here too, so we can't escape!
You're not gonna run?
Who are you saying that to?
No matter what comes, I'll stop it.
It looks like I'll be able
to perform a wonderful melody.
Damn it, a caster who put up the barrier?
And that monster's almost on us.
We're gonna be doomed at this rate.
- Save us!
- I don't wanna die yet!
Done for... We're all done for.
Help! Someone, help us!
Why did things end up this way?
And I haven't gone
on my honeymoon yet!
Lord Abel.
- This time, we're done for!
- It's all over for Easton!
What? Crap!
We won't make it in time.
How...
Why...
It's being dragged back.
Is that magic?
No, the barrier nullifies all magic.
Which means, that's likely...
It's him!
Impossible.
Huh? No way.
Ever since I met you...
I've always, always felt this way.
But this is simply
way too ridiculous, Mash.
Hey, that...
Isn't that Mash Burnedead?
Y-You're kidding me.
He's playing...
...tug-of-war with it!
But is it all right?
He can't use magic, right?
Can someone like that
be at the top of this school?
We can't allow that.
There's no room for someone
who can't use magic in this world.
Yeah. I mean, how'd he even...
Does it really matter, though?
Whether or not you can use magic...
Right now, he's fighting
for us and the school.
He's giving everything he's got
to fight for us!
You can do it.
- You can do it.
You can do it, Mash.
Mash Burnedead.
You can do it, Mash!
Mash!
I would never have imagined this.
Mash, who was always scolded at school.
Mash, who was about to be expelled.
Mash, who can't use magic.
He's overriding every rule in this world
where magic is everything.