Thirteen ancient wands
are said to exist in the Magic Realm.
The wands choose only those
with innate talents
and bestow blessings upon their wielders.
These wands are called the Master Canes.
The qualifying round for the Divine Visionary
Candidate Exam, "The Life Crystal."
Each team has three members, and they strive
to break the crystals of opposing teams.
However...
It's...
It's a team match.
So why are we forced to split apart!?
Damn it!
What a problem.
I have to go find Finn.
Are we totally screwed now?
I gotta find him real fast.
I'm sure they're in bad shape right now.
Crap, crap, crap.
Mash and Dot don't have
their crystals anymore.
This is the one crystal we have left.
I have to guard it with my life.
I-I'm sorry.
Please forgive me!
Carpaccio.
There's a knife in his shoulder.
Our birth decides
who can climb to the peak.
Talent is not distributed evenly.
That's why you need to live the life
you were made for.
Got that, weakling?
He's worse than bad news to go that far!
If I were to run into him now...
He's on the move.
Will he catch on
because I made noise while running?
I have to lay low here.
All right. I need to sever
my presence as organic matter.
I am a wall. Stay away.
I am a wall. I'm a wall. I'm a...
He's gone. I successfully became a wall.
What are you doing?
I am a wall.
You're funny.
H-Help me!
Please. I'll lick your shoes.
I'll even lick between your toes.
Please help me!
You... You're Finn Ames.
Huh? How does he know me?
The continuing student
who barely made the cutoff.
I've become famous in the worst way!
I remember you well.
I was wondering
how someone like this is at Easton.
And yet, here you are
at the Divine Visionary Candidate Exam.
Did your brother get you in?
I feel nothing but dissatisfaction
when I see talentless trash like you.
Give me that crystal.
It's not suitable for the likes of you.
Hurry up and hand it over.
He's so scary!
This is totally intimidating.
But...
this crystal holds Mash's future.
The choice I need to make...
Protect this crystal to the...
Why am I suddenly bleeding?
Magic?
What did you just try to do?
You're weak but acting like a big shot.
I'm asking you.
What did you just try to do?
Oh, this is that distinct feeling
I get when I'm truly terrified.
My blood vessels are squeezed shut,
and my heart is clamped down by a cold chill.
Surely you're aware
of the difference in our abilities.
You're going to lose that crystal anyway.
Be submissive and had it over.
It's better to not feel any pain.
You don't want to end up like that, do you?
I won't say it again.
Now, give it up.
I'd say we've got
three standouts in this exam.
Mash Burnedead, who can't use magic.
Lance Crown, the top transfer student.
And...
Carpaccio Luo-yang,
the top continuing student.
But I always imagined he was like me
with no interest
in becoming a Divine Visionary.
I'd guess Orter Madl cut him a deal,
like he did with me.
Carpaccio is a prodigy, chosen by
a wand fit to be a national treasure.
It's not an exaggeration to say
he's the most talented in our academy.
Not quite mature. An unripe fruit.
Blessings from the earth...
My gratitude to all living creatures...
And Daddy and Mommy, thank you
for bringing me into this world.
I don't get it.
That crystal will end up as mine anyway.
Don't give up.
If I can protect this crystal
during this showdown...
Now is my chance,
as he's totally underestimating me.
I haven't used my personal magic yet.
That's what I'm betting on.
Dangerousse!
Nothing is happening?
A lie so he could escape.
I can catch up soon enough.
Changeas!
This is where I crushed the first crystal.
The student I beat earlier is gone.
Magic that switches locations.
The reason Finn didn't use his magic
until now was to catch me off guard?
All right. I gained quite a bit of distance.
It was the right decision to save
my personal magic till the end.
I'll make my escape...
What? My leg...
It hurts... Damn it...
Footsteps?
This is bad.
Is this your last-ditch effort?
You already understand, don't you?
The difference between you and me!
Now, give it here.
Weakling. You need to step down.
What is that magic? He transfers damage?
That's going way too far.
Enough alre—
No...
I will not give this to you.
But I really am glad.
To have a great guy like you for a friend.
Even if I'm a loser...
Even if I'm a coward...
Let's come back again sometime.
I can't do it.
I can't do something as pathetic
as abandoning my friend!
Nalcos!
Nalco—
That's enough. How abominable.
Incompetent people who make
an effort irritate me the most.
I will show you
that all your efforts are in vain.
Hey, this is looking bad.
If he cuts his neck...
I will not...
- Stop.
- If he keeps going, it'll kill him.
No matter what, I will not...
It wasn't in vain.
Because I'm here now.
Finn...
Thank you.
Mash.
Sorry I'm so late.
Huh?
What does this mean?
I'm incapable of feeling pain.
What's that?
My wand is special.
What nonsense are you talking...
Mash's attacks are reflecting back at him?
My magic transfers damage I take
back to my opponent.
So if I get hurt...
Mash!
His wounds healed?
On the other hand, all pain I suffer
is absorbed by this wand.
I don't control it.
The inability to be hurt
is the blessing of the Master Cane,
the most ancient of wands.
This power was automatically activated
the moment it chose me.
Thus, from the moment I was born,
I've never felt any pain.
The most ancient of wands,
of which there are only 13.
He's making full use of a Master Cane.
Bona fide talent
acknowledged as a chosen one.
We sure have a good crop
of first-years this year.
I would like to feel pain.
But someone of your caliber
is a far cry from dealing pain to me.
Let's hurry up and end this.
He stabs himself
to damage his opponent.
It's an unavoidable attack.
That's useless.
No attack can give me any pain.
It's no good. All the damage
is reflected back to Mash.
It's like Carpaccio
is always on the offense!
You can't even call this a fight.
This is a farce.
A person's fate is determined
by the abilities they are born with.
What you're doing now
is for self-satisfaction.
Completely useless.
The same can be said
for Finn Ames over there.
A loser from back in middle school.
Always compared to his brother,
but always on the verge of flunking.
He's out of place to begin with.
People like him don't belong here.
He can't even protect
a single crystal on his own.
He's a weakling,
always being saved by others...
You're an eyesore, Finn.
You have a point.
It's wiser to quit something
if you can't do it.
And it's important to look at yourself
objectively so you can know your place.
Finn's actions in your eyes
may be futile efforts,
and he may be an eyesore.
But...
desperately standing against
something you fear...
My friend is standing against someone
overwhelmingly stronger than himself.
And to thoughtlessly laugh
and look down on him...
I won't allow that.
Mash.
Consecutive attacks?
If Mash incurs any further damage...
Consecutive attacks
so the healing speed can't keep up.
Useless. Such a simple tactic
to attempt to break through.
I had the slightest bit
of expectation from him.
But what a shame.
What? A crack in the Goddess Statue?
Did the Goddess Statue
actually have a capacity limit?
Impossible.
This has never happened before.
Of course, I'm a million times
stronger than you are.
But when you realize that, can you
stand against me like Finn stood against you?
Mash.
What kind of body does this guy have?
Damn him.
This is the first time someone
cracked the Goddess Statue.
But the Goddess Statue
triggers automatically.
It simply becomes more defensive
the more attacks I withstand.
I won't kill you right away.
I feel elated...
to the fact that such a human existed.
In this world, where everything...
is nothing but a haze.
An iron wand?
No way!
He's sculpting the iron wand
with the strength of his fingers?
BAM
He made a tennis racket!?
He's dodging the syringes
while targeting repeated shots
at that one crack
in the Goddess Statue!?
Is he...
playing wall rally with that nurse?
Impossible.
If you want to know that badly,
I'll teach you.
FWIP FWIP
What pain is.
Wasn't that a bit excessive?
Come on, you're kidding me.
Is that even possible?
Carpaccio, a savant
chosen by a Master Cane.
He was just defeated by something
similar to wall-hitting tennis!
A decisive victory
against a Master Cane user.
Um, Mash...
I'm sorry, it's my fault.
Thank you.
I'm a klutz, and I always trouble others.
But I can still stay together
with everyone thanks to you.
Thank you.
Yeah. I'm glad.
So this is pain...
I can't stop bleeding...
And the pain spreads with each heartbeat.
It hurts... It hurts...
So pain is something...
this horrifying, huh?
Such a...
He withstood this much pain
for someone else?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
But when you realize that,
can you stand against me like Finn did?
Indeed, the difference is obvious.
I was utterly outmatched.