Well done. Now leave the rest to...
H-Help...
Orter...
Kaldo, I hear you have sided
with Mash Burnedead.
To be swayed simply
from a small show of brawn...
How you have fallen.
I will not accept him.
It's not like I fully accept him, either.
But his strength is legitimate,
if nothing else.
There may come a time
when you'll have to accept that.
Several days later,
news of Innocent Zero's assault on Easton
Magic Academy had spread across the world.
To stem the chaos, the official story was that
the Divine Visionaries drove him off.
However, many had their doubts about that.
Following this incident,
the Bureau of Magic responded by fortifying
security and regulating information.
Mash, the center of this incident and
the only one who knew the truth,
was burdened by this grave knowledge...
and went to the beach.
Why?
Hittin' the beach in the summer is a must!
I've never seen a beach before.
I've never been to the beach
with friends before.
Me neither.
Let's all have fun.
- Yup.
- Yeah!
Whee! Whee!
Well, they're all
on the quirky side, so...
But should we be here,
given everything that's happened?
Dummy! This is exactly the time
to play watermelon smash!
'Tis the season.
Okay, here's a slaughtermelon.
WRIGGLE WRIGGLE
What's that!?
I see. So I have to smash it ope...
SHLOOP
Show an opening and it'll suck your blood.
Worst case scenario, you die.
Freaky, creepy, scary!
Why did you bring such a thing!?
Whatcha talkin' about?
Life is a constant struggle.
You kill or be killed.
What's this all of a sudden?
Your eyes are glazed over!
Okay, I smashed it. Let's eat.
Thank... you... Thank... y...ou...
So hard to eat!
But I can't believe Mash
was Innocent Zero's child.
Considering Mash's circumstances,
they're going to make him
take the fall somehow.
He hasn't done anything wrong, though.
Things are going the opposite way
of the peace Mash is hoping for.
For Mash, the greatest trial yet
is about to happen.
Headmaster!
What are you doing here?
It's summertime.
But your injuries...
There's nothing to worry ab...
You really are badly injured!
Why did you make an effort to come here?
Summer only comes once a year.
No, but still...
As you all know,
Mash Burnedead will never know peace
unless we defeat Innocent Zero.
On top of his time magic,
the most powerful of personal magics,
he has my spatial magic.
And he's amplified its effectiveness
with forbidden magic.
You can say that Innocent Zero is the greatest
magic user in Magic Realm history.
That's not all.
The five brothers who flank him
are all top-tier magic users in this world.
They match my powers, if not more.
To think five people who are that powerful
are on the enemy side...
At this rate, the world
will surely come to an end.
I didn't expect Innocent Zero
to amass this much power.
As we stand now,
our chance of victory is nearly zero.
However, I believe the uncertainty
that can overcome that is Mash Burnedead.
Through physical training, he gained
instantaneous power, toughness, mental fortitude,
and absurd strength.
This absurd strength surely will be the key
to break through the strongest of magics.
But, for all Mash is, he can't just go up against
the strongest magic user in the world.
Lemon, it will be all right.
Either I'll win, or I'll lose.
That's one in two. A 50% chance.
And muscles never lose.
HONK
So the chances of winning are 100%.
What an unintelligent line of reasoning.
That's what I love about him.
And most off all, there's his spirit.
Always optimistic, never abandoning the weak.
Such a heart is where true strength dwells.
Please make into reality
the world that I could not create.
I'm counting on you, Mash Burnedead.
Leave it to me.
I'll beat up all the enemies,
and then, I will definitely graduate
from this school with everyone.
Mash.
But the end-of-semester exams
are coming up.
Are you really okay?
One failed exam
and you're immediately expelled.
By the way, old man...
There are end-of-semester exams
before the Divine Visionary Elect Final Exam.
Is Mushroom Head gonna be okay?
Mash is a kind soul,
so he will be all right.
What does kindness
have to do with exams?
We gave Mash a mock exam
to see where he stands now.
Magical Linguistics, 30 points.
Magic History, 10 points.
Potions, 3 points.
Magical Mathematics, 10 points.
SHK SHK SHK SHK SHK
He scraped by through the hands-on exams,
so his written exams are abysmal.
He's deranged.
He really hates studying, doesn't he?
I wanna go home.
Well, don't worry.
All of us will support ya.
Huh? Dot, you do well academically?
I sure do.
Studying is the most visible form
of effort made to achieve a goal.
So I study a little bit every day,
thinking it's practice for putting in effort.
And you lose nothing from having
an academic background.
I don't want to have any regrets
once I grow up.
SHK SHK SHK SHK SHK
I'm somehow hurt by this.
Don't you worry.
I'll teach you what you need.
Teach me pleash...
GNASH
GRIN
All right, let's get to it.
'Kay.
We'll start with the basics
for Magical Mathematics.
We'll ignore the practical applications
and go straight for test points.
'Kay.
What's important is to memorize
the formulas, and how you adapt them.
We'll do Magic History next.
First, we can learn the terminology,
then connect them together into a line.
Once you're able to do that...
Magical Linguistics is a piece of cake
if you learn techniques to be clever!
The ones you really need to get down
is this formula and...
For Magical Studies,
it's important to learn
the system of magics first,
then break it down
into smaller subdivisions.
For instance, this...
What's wrong?
I heard an explosion!
Mash!
I can't...
I can't bring myself
to think I can do this at all. Ever.
It's not a matter of can or can't!
If you can't, you'll be expelled.
Evil... So brutal...
Glance.
Mash!?
Mash?
He made a run for it!
Mash!
- We have to hurry after him!
- Stop. Don't chase him.
Lance?
Consequences aside,
if he runs from difficult situations,
then that's just the kind of person he is.
But...
I'm not bored enough to teach someone
who isn't willing to learn.
But...
I'm still gonna go look for him.
Finn!
Where did Mash go?
He's buried? Into the ground?
I want to return to the earth like this.
Mash.
I'm sorry, Finn.
Studying is the one thing I can't...
That's not like you, Mash.
The Mash I know
doesn't think twice when taking on
even the most impossible opponents.
I want to graduate together with you.
Together with you, Mash!
Let's give it some effort, okay?
Thank you, Finn.
It really is like what you just said.
I showed you a pathetic side of myself.
I'll try my best.
What's with all the moles attached to you?
I'm sorry for running away.
Please teach me one more time.
Oh man, what should I do?
I'm not motivated—
Let's try our best, Mash!
Huh?
Sorry, I'm kidding.
I jest. Did I look petty?
Maybe I looked like a really petty guy?
To your seat.
'Kay.
Please don't ignore me.
I'm seriously sorry.
And thus, Mash confronted studying,
which he was not so good at.
And on exam day...
Now, begin!
- This is it.
- Egalt Vansom.
You'll be okay, Mash!
Graduate with everyone...
Next. Mash Burnedead.
Oh, here.
Mash Burnedead.
You have always had a rebellious attitude
towards classes at this academy.
SLUMP
I didn't mean to be...
On top of that,
your grades are usually atrocious.
I'd like to say it's only a matter of time
before you are expelled.
But it seems you can
put in the effort on occasion.
These are...
Your marks are not what I'd call
praiseworthy, however.
You scraped by!
Just barely.
BAM
Welp, easy peasy.
Don't get cocky.
Bamboo it!
What?
That's a huge problem!
They understand what he's saying?
Bamboo it!
It's in the newspaper that
the prestigious Easton Academy has
a Lackmagic as Divine Visionary candidate.
Even Lance can understand.
Bamboo, bamboo, bamboo-bamboo it!
What the!?
All the civilians who read the newspaper
are rushing onto campus!?
Hand over Mash Burnedead!
What do you mean,
there's a Lackmagic here!?
Banish him from the magic school at once!
Quit hiding and show yourself!
It's unheard of that a Lackmagic attends
the top academy of the Magic Realm!
You're letting a blight-blood
on the platform of God's holy festival?
That's an act of blasphemy against God!
Not good. They're too worked up
and can't calm down.
Who the hell are you?
Unrelated guys stay the hell out!
Hold on just a second!
Lemon.
Just because he can't use magic,
how does that effect all of you?
Does a person's worth
depend on their magic skills?
I disagree.
At the point he can't use magic,
he's been forsaken by God!
He's not like us!
What do you have to do with him?
Outsiders should stay out!
I'm not an outsider!
I am...
Mash Burnedead's...
wife.
He was already married?
At that young an age?
HONK
Oh, brother.
Maybe not a wife but more like a soulmate!
The red string of fate
tightly binds us together!
Gimme a break!
Be a bit serious, will ya?
Huh? Got a problem with that, punks!?
You wanna bring it on?
What's with this girl?
They're being awfully noisy
for nameless characters.
Wait!
You are...
I am Mash Burnedead's...
agent.
Agent?
What's that?
I will now read a prepared statement
from Mr. Burnedead.
To all of you who can use magic.
It is such an honor for someone inexperienced
like myself to be chosen as a candidate.
I may come across as audacious,
but please let me say one thing.
I'll kill you.
That is all.
Enough of the jokes!
Are you picking a fight with us!?
HONK
Why is he making things
even more complicated?
I am going to defend him!
He did no wrong!
Defending someone with no magic
makes you full-fledged criminals, too!
Sinners! Accept your judgement!
Lemon!
Hold it. It'll get more convoluted if you go.
You need to endure for now.
You chickening out?
Is that it?
It's fine.
Mash not being able to use magic...
If Mash is going to be judged
for such a ridiculous reason,
I will take the punishment with him!
No matter how many stones
or insults you throw...
Such a... Such a...
Wh-Why did you bother
to come back and save me?
Well...
If your reason was similar to mine,
I'd kinda feel sorry for you.
Such a kind person...
cannot be evil! I believe in him!
You're being emotional.
That shows what a kid you are.
If I capture the Lackmagic Divine Visionary
candidate, I will instantly be famous.
What a shame.
Lackmagics have no human rights!
DOOM
That girl is also a sinner,
corrupting our world's order!
Show no mercy!
Damn sinners!!
Lemon!
Mash.
It's Mash Burnedead!
Don't let him get away!
Catching someone
who can't use magic is child's play.
Mash! Hide yourself
inside school campus for now!
Prison Wall!
Mash!
I am the one who caught him!
Those walls are 15 cm thick.
Even giant monsters are ever so easily
trapped in here!
It's an amazing cage.
No, that's not...
The walls are 15 cm thick.
Even giant monsters are ever so easily
trapped in here.
No, just no!
The walls are 15 cm thick.
Even giant monsters are ever so easily
trapped in here.
The walls are 15 cm thick.
Even giant monsters are ever so easily
trapped in here.
Hey, Mash.
Well, that's how it's been for a long time,
and you might not be satisfied for now.
But I will become the best in this
Magic Realm and prove it to you...
that it's okay even if you can't use magic.
Apologies. My arbitrary decision
has caused confusion within you all.
Headmaster Wahlberg!
However, his fate will be determined
after the Divine Visionary
Candidate Exam.
It's been decided by the Bureau of Magic.
In the meantime, we ask for your patience
for just a little while longer.
Mash Burnedead.
In one's life, you may never come across
even one person
who will speak up on your behalf.
You have excellent friends.
I'm proud of you all.
Since entering this school,
I've received so many things that I hold dear.
That's why...
I will make sure to become
a Divine Visionary.
If you cannot become
a Divine Visionary,
the Magic Realm will criminalize
even those who defended you.
Passing the exam is the only path,
Mash Burnedead.
The Candidate Exam
has come to its final stage.
Mash, cheered on by marvelous friends
he met at Easton Magic Academy...
Receiving yells of support from kind upperclassmen
who accepted his existence.
With bonds strengthened through
battles against rivals in his heart,
he seeks to become the Divine Visionary!
No matter what comes my way,
I'll knock the stuffing out of them...
with my fist!