Wahlberg and Innocent Zero
face each other high in the air.
Innocent Zero used magic to rewind time,
and revived the body of Adam Jobs,
who was previously their mentor.
He then had one of his death row henchmen,
Necross, control Adam and attack.
However, even Adam's most powerful
dark magic didn't work against Wahlberg.
The headmaster is really strong.
On the ground, Mash reflected attacks
from Innocent Zero's core member, Cell War,
and Mash choked him in a second flat.
I care a lot about this school.
If you're claiming to destroy it,
I'll choke you out as many times
as I need to...
with my muscles.
Mash is also really strong.
In the skies near Easton, Ryoh and
Nerey Shawn took two whole episodes
to finally arrive at Easton Magic Academy.
Mr. Ryoh, it really took a long time,
but we're almost at Easton Magic Academy.
That's a great narration, Nerey.
But you have to say it before
the narrator to be hot stuff.
Like me.
Isn't it useless to fix your hairdo
while flying?
Oh, now you want to shun me, Shawn?
But you know, taking care of your appearance
is elementary for a hot guy.
So awesome!
Wait, this is no time for that.
Let's hurry.
Innocent Zero is at Easton...
What's wrong, Nerey?
Nerey is...
He's frozen, unable to narrate
his own condition.
This means, someone
has cast magic that stops time,
and Nerey has entered the stoppage field.
Which means, I can assume those with low
magical power have all been stopped.
Sorry, Nerey.
I'm going ahead without you.
I hope Mushroom Head who
Innocent Zero is after is all right.
Kaldo! Orter!
Ryoh.
Both of you were all right.
But to defeat this many of them,
I'd expect nothing less from Divine Visionaries.
Such hot stuff.
It wasn't just us.
There seem to be many
excellent students here at Easton.
Oh, what happened to Mushroom Head?
Wasn't he being targeted
by Innocent Zero?
He's fine.
More than that, he even defeated
one of Innocent Zero's core members.
Replenish calories... Replenish calories...
What a guy.
Not only did he defeat a core member,
but he's elegantly enjoying some sweets.
More importantly, Mr. Wahlberg
is fighting against Innocent Zero.
What? Where?
We don't know.
So that students don't get roped
into the fight against Innocent Zero,
he most likely used transfer magic
to move elsewhere.
I have no idea where he is now.
Oh, then I'll go look for him.
Go look?
How?
HONK
With my muscles.
Let's see what he's got.
There is no way an anomaly who
can't use detection magic can find him.
Anyway...
I will interrogate this man and figure out
everything Innocent Zero is after.
That's the most efficient, logical procedure.
Divine Visionaries are executors
of the laws of this realm.
Evil that defy laws
are sure to be convicted!
A barrier to nullify all magic.
Transfer magic.
That core member was unconscious.
It wasn't magic he used
on his own, which means...
Someone on Innocent Zero's side
is still lurking around here.
Let's investigate.
Now we can't move around too carelessly.
If we leave this area,
the students will get harmed.
We should avoid that.
We don't know what will happen.
All of you stand-by here as well!
I'm sorry we can't head over
to help you, Mr. Wahlberg.
However, you are the embodiment
of Noblesse Oblige.
I'm sure you would do
the same thing yourself.
Noblesse Oblige.
The strong are there to help the weak.
If Mr. Wahlberg is the weak,
then the one to go rescue him is me,
the next number one man
of this realm!
You better make sure to find him,
Mushroom Head.
After me, you're the hottest thing right now.
This is the first time
I've seen it in decades.
Space Sacrifice.
You still show no deterioration,
Wahlberg.
It's your turn next, right,
Innocent Zero?
Noblesse Oblige.
Well, you'll figure it out someday.
Because you are strong.
Master. Leave everything to me now.
He's coming.
Timez Cold!
Time stoppage magic.
Spaces.
He cut out the space around himself.
I'm in his blind spot.
Spaces Bout!
When did he manipulate time?
Timez Rewound!
Your legs are next, Wahlberg.
He's exploiting the openings
right when I attack.
And using powerful magic
as stopping time this frequently...
He had grown this much, huh?
You monster.
If so...
I will cut out this whole space!
Spaces Bout Stampede!
Not just that.
To keep him from abusing
the time lag against me,
I will keep cutting this space away!
I will carve it all out,
time stoppage magic and all!
It'll take more than that
to defeat me, Wahlberg.
When did you...
He stopped time
right before space was carved out!
Timez Rewound!
Wh...
It's useless, Wahlberg.
There is too much of a power gap
between us.
I was only interested in myself.
I had ambitions.
I was willing to make sacrifices.
But you? Your eyes kept wandering
to others to protect.
You became unable to prioritize yourself.
Humans with no egos are weak, Wahlberg.
This is a result of you abasing
yourself so that others will like you.
What a shame.
Is one's life really only for one's self?
I was born frail of body.
My grades weren't outstanding
and I was cowardly.
There was no place for me in school,
and of course I had no friends.
With no reason to go,
I started to stay home from school.
A lack of confidence made me fearful.
I didn't want to be rejected by others.
So before I could be rejected, I severed
opportunities to interact with people.
Gradually I felt this world was bland
and boring, and became very pessimistic.
And that was when I met...
Did you know capybaras run
at 50 km per hour? Come to school.
Master Adam.
Did you know dolphins drown
if they sleep? Come to school.
He made repeated unauthorized visits
to my place, always with strange animal trivia.
Did you know pigs can't look up at the sky
because of their physiology? Come to school.
No matter how many times
I rejected him...
Did you know that dogs can tolerate hot food
even less than humans? Come to school.
No matter how bad the weather,
or no matter how coldly
I treated him...
Master tried to involve himself with me.
Did you know that giraffes sleep
only 20 minutes a day? Come to school.
Time and time again.
One day, I asked him.
Why do you go this far?
How do I put it?
I just can't leave you alone.
Hearing those words saved me.
That one sentence...
Huh? You laughed?
His actions, his smile.
Innocent Zero.
It's fine to live
for your own sake as you do.
But I have lived to this day, saved
by all of the goodwill around me.
So for me to abandon those weaker
than me... That will not happen.
You plan on unleashing it here,
Wahlberg?
Though it may cost me my life...
I will not change my ideals.
The ideals that Master has taught me!
Even among triple-liners, very few
are allowed access to the epitome of magic.
Spaces Thirds!
Uranus Inclination!
Thirds spells unleash the power
of the gods residing in the wands.
Your power certainly
hasn't declined with age.
You surely are aware...
The power of Uranus, the god of the sky.
Unavoidable space carving magic.
Wahlberg, how dare you.
Timez Cold!
What the...
It's useless. Within this space,
any magic can be transferred.
There's nowhere to run, Innocent Zero.
That's how far you will go to...
That's right. This is the least I can do
as headmaster.
Uranus World Delete!
With this, I will sever the affinity I have had
with you for such a long time, Innocent Zero!
Timez Unmove.
I have stopped all time within this space.
No manner of attack
can affect me, who can control time.
Your loss was destined from the moment
you chose to fight against me.
As an old friend,
I will instantly send you to your grave.
Timez Arrow Rain.
You won't survive with those wounds.
I delivered a fatal blow
to the caster, yet the magic...
Thirds unleashes the true power
within the wand.
If you load it with maximum magical power,
even if the caster were to die,
the will of the wand
will cast the spell on its own.
That's foolish. You can't...
I had been saving up my magical power
this whole time for that.
It can't be...
My Thirds will tear you apart...
in exchange for my own life.
You planned this from the beginning.
I have not fulfilled my duty yet.
I've been watching the whole time.
The kind students who desperately
protected their friends' futures.
A student who is determined to change
the rules of this world to save his little sister.
And a kind-hearted student who seeks to become
a Divine Visionary, protect his friends,
and correct mistakes so he can live
with his grandfather even without magic.
This world could be so much better.
It could be a world filled with kindness,
where we respect each other
and accept our weaknesses.
That is why I must save them.
Those weak, fragile souls.
They who were like me long ago.
People who are irrationally
being tormented...
And for that purpose, I must spearhead
the effort and lead the others.
Noblesse Oblige.
Like my master did for me.
To laugh together...
I will show it with my own actions.
To my students!
That light...
Wh-What's that?
Magic!
That is spatial magic.
Which means... It can't be!
It's the four seasons of omnipotence!
Wh-What in the world is that?
This is outrageous.
Mr. Wahlberg didn't...
Why is it shrinking?
Spatial magic is activated
in an expanded area.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Innocent Zero.
The spell hasn't activated.
Is it possible that he reversed time?
Such a giant space as that?
The entire thing?
Timez Arrow Rain.
Spaces Bout.
Wahlberg. You are strong.
But I will become even stronger.
I live only for my own sake.
You cannot surpass me.
I will show you proof right now.
How cruel is fate...
So our ideals are doomed,
never to be realized...
Was the world I envisioned so fragile
that such a small-minded belief
can crush it underfoot?
Alas...
Farewell, Wahlberg.