At Easton Magic Academy,
each dorm is overseen by a prefect.
The three prefects boasts
some of the greatest talent in Easton.
All of them have the skills necessary
to become a Divine Visionary.
A few years ago, a tournament was held for
13-15 year olds in the middle school division.
One magic user singlehandedly
overpowered all the other competitors.
They had only been nine at the time.
Their name was Margarette Macaron.
The future prefect of Orca dorm.
Well, well. If it isn't the Sword Cane...
Rayne Ames.
Of all people...
Not only will I face Mash Burnedead,
but a Divine Visionary
will also entertain me?
But you are...
The powerless... winter.
What the hell is going on here?
Not every powerful magic user
strives to be a Divine Visionary.
"Divine Visionary" is just a title, after all.
Compared to myself who genuinely
sought nothing but strength,
and you who sought a superficial position.
Which one of us is stronger?
Partisan.
Sounds.
Okay, I'll roll first.
A 67.
Let's see...
"Easily duped by a scheming beauty's
charm spell. Lose five million Lond."
What the hell!?
This board game's a piece of crap!
Oh, no!
I'm next.
A 25.
"Head to holding cell for restraining
a love interest like a stalker."
"Skip 320 turns."
This board game might be dangerous
as it may predict our futures.
"Your little sister suddenly brings home
a boyfriend. Return to start"!?
"Return a lost item to the police.
Earn 100 Lond."
I'm glad.
All right. Guess I'm next.
A 98.
Let's see...
"It's discovered you can't use magic,
and you are executed."
"Game over."
Game over!?
Gotta laugh. Just gotta laugh it off!
What's up with this board game!?
- Graviole. Graviole. Graviole.
- Just let 'em try!
- Yeah, let 'em try!
- Graviole. Graviole. Graviole.
- Just let 'em try!
I never dreamed he'd be surrounded
by such wonderful friends.
I hope it lasts forever.
I'm sure it will.
- I'm the future wife, you hear?
- More like, what the hell is this thing!?
I have to keep it going.
Partisan!
Shiver Sounds!
Howling Sounds!
I wouldn't attack if I were you.
They'll explode in response
to your spellcasting.
Rayne Ames.
Do you know why we desire stimulation?
Art, love, sports, drinking,
drugs, gambling...
None of these things are necessary
to live a normal life.
So why seek them?
The answer is simple.
Because boredom is as good as death.
We live for those stimulations.
Yet, you...
You're awfully easygoing,
meddling in other's business.
How boring.
I can't imagine someone with values
like you could ever fulfill me.
Be a dear and step aside.
I've got to see Mash Burnedead.
He's a brazen kid.
Brazen enough to tell me...
that he will become a Divine Visionary
even without magic.
That he will change the perception
of this world.
His mood shifted?
If he went against Margarette, not even
Lord Rayne would walk away unscathed.
Rayne may act aloof,
but he always takes care of others.
By the way, Nerey...
What do you know about marks?
Well, the number of marks increases
in accordance with your absolute magic power?
Correct.
Easton Magic Academy has had
many double-liners cross our step, of course.
But there have only been an extremely
small number of triple-liners.
If two lines means magic itself
recognizes their talent,
then those with three lines
must be chosen by the gods.
The summer... of bliss.
And the youngest to ever
acquire three lines is...
the one named Rayne Ames.
Change the perception of this world...
I'll make sure that brazen kid
goes as far as he can go.
"It's discovered
you can't use magic. Executed."
I'm gonna get some fresh air.
He acts cool,
but it must be eating him up inside.
Of course it is.
He didn't do anything wrong.
If I were in his shoes,
I would keep blaming society.
No one will ever spot me out here.
I can't eat this specialty cream puff
in everyone's presence.
A triple-liner. A talent gifted by the gods.
To find someone my age
who's achieved that level.
Just how blessed am I?
Howling Sounds will create a chain explosion
in reaction to chanting.
He may be a triple-liner,
but he has to chant to use magic.
Orter Madl put you up to this, didn't he?
It's not like you to take an interest
in school affairs, but you're here.
This pretty much has to be
Orter Madl's doing.
Dear me. I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Your target Mash Burnedead
can't use magic.
In this world, lack of magic
is basically having no human rights.
An ordinary human
would feel despair, no doubt.
Jealous of those who can use magic,
regretting being ever born, hating society...
All of those would be reasonable reactions.
But Mash Burnedead is different.
He...
fights against his own destiny.
Not that an underhanded rat like you
would ever understand.
Oh my. What a darling little speech.
But...
I couldn't care less.
They remain confident despite facing down
a triple-liner Divine Visionary.
They're not being cocky, though.
They distributed their coins to the dorm, saying
they weren't interested in Divine Visionaries.
But they took a total of ten gold coins
from upperclassmen, more than anyone last year.
Besides, Howling Sounds will end
the moment he chants a counterspell.
This shows Margarette Macaron's
overwhelming talent.
I hear it... The unending applause...
Sounds Orchestra.
Now you're forced to cast a spell.
Checkmate.
Um... What exactly distinguishes
a triple-liner from a double-liner?
Three lines signify one chosen by the gods.
They can unleash more power
than a double-liner, of course.
But that is hardly all they can do.
They can awaken
a wand's dormant true form.
True form?
Yes, that's correct. The reason why
lies behind magic being a gift from the gods.
Howling Sounds was drowned out
without being activated?
Summon Ares.
In other words, their power calls upon
a god's strength from within a wand.
His wand is changing form!?
So this is what was given to Divine Visionary
Rayne Ames, the title of a god's wand...
"Sword Cane."
Checkmate.
Black Partisan.
Sounds Shield!
U-Um, I guess I should say thanks.
For what? I was just playing
with some rabbits in the forest.
So you are a fan of rabbits.
The selection exam is soon.
Yes.
I'm terrible at encouraging people.
But I'll say one thing.
You're embarking on a challenge the likes
of which this world has never seen.
Nothing good will ever come
from your failure.
So win.
And give your challenge meaning.
'Kay.
You kids are so sloppy.
So that's a triple-liner.
The gigantic wand raises
the baseline magic power output.
Even entry-level spells have the effectiveness
of Secondth magic.
I could have tried my own Secondth spell,
but I put their safety as my priority.
Is this maternal instinct?
Margarette, I'm sorry.
No worries.
As they all say,
you save the best for last.
Afterwards...
These are the coins we got from Lang.
Three per person sound good?
Let's do our best on the selection exam.
I can't!
I'm sorry!
It'll be soon. Wait for me, Anna.
STARE
I'm too hyped to sleep!
Guess I'll check my luggage.
Water bottle, handkerchief,
bug repellant, tissue.
And then eye drops, antacid,
pain reliever, laxative.
Facial toner, antiperspirant,
breath freshener.
Mash, I heard from your friends.
Everyone has discovered
that you can't use magic?
And that you will be charged with this crime
if you don't meet their demands.
I'm sorry. This is my doing.
If only I could have given you a normal life.
If only I could have provided you
a life without inconveniences.
If I had done more to hide it all to the end.
But I'm happy.
I have you who always
looks out for me so much.
I was able to go to school even for
a little bit, and was blessed with friends.
I got to eat lots of cream puffs, too.
So I'm happy.
Thank you, Pops.
Good. Now come back safe and sound.
The path to Divine Visionary
is broadly divided into three stages.
The first is coin acquisition.
The second is
the Divine Visionary Candidate Exam.
The third is
the Divine Visionary Elect Final Exam.
One must acquire five or more gold coins
to advance to the second stage.
MOORE TOMATO
LANG DORM THIRD-YEAR,
THREE GOLD COINS
However, due to Innocent Zero's intervention,
the exam has been pushed forward.
DOLB MARX
LANG DORM THIRD-YEAR,
THREE GOLD COINS
PON TORUS
ORCA DORM SECOND-YEAR,
THREE GOLD COINS
LEBLANC RUSSELL
LANG DORM SECOND-YEAR,
THREE GOLD COINS
Only three gold coins are needed to qualify.
MAX LAND
ADLER DORM THIRD-YEAR,
THREE GOLD COINS
AORIO MORRIS
ADLER DORM THIRD-YEAR,
THREE GOLD COINS
DOT BARRETT
ADLER DORM FIRST-YEAR,
THREE GOLD COINS
FINN AMES
ADLER DORM FIRST-YEAR,
THREE GOLD COINS
CARPACCIO LUO-YANG
ORCA DORM FIRST-YEAR,
FOUR GOLD COINS
Magic is the crux of our society!
It is everything!
LANCE CROWN
ADLER DORM FIRST-YEAR,
FIVE GOLD COINS
Those without magic have no rights!
MARGARETTE MACARON
ORCA DORM THIRD-YEAR,
FIVE GOLD COINS
Here we have the magic users
who are the pinnacle of this society!
The examinees have entered the arena!
It seems even Margarette Macaron
will enter this year.
You face a difficult road, Mash Burnedead.
MASH BURNEDEAD
ADLER DORM FIRST-YEAR,
SEVEN GOLD COINS
Humans are defined by a standard.
Existences like you who disrupt
the entire system are not human.
As long as I'm around, your existence
will never be acknowledged by this world.
CLNCH CLNCH CLNCH
"That's not necessarily true."
"It's fine!"
"You can do it if you try!"
"Go for it."
Thanks, Kevin, Tom, Mike, Kim,
Yamada, Koji, Satomi, Yukari.
I'll do my best.
I'll take you on then.
With all I've got.
Now, the last one to enter...
Adler dorm, Mash Burnedead!
Hey, that Mash guy...
Isn't he the one who can't use magic?
If that's true, him being
in the selection exam is unprecedented.
This is no place for you!
Go home!
That's right, go home!
Go home! Go home!
Go home!
Come on! Someone like him might ruin
the prestige of Divine Visionaries!
What do you say about that, admins!?
What a bunch of bullies.
Mash earned the right
to be here by winning coins.
His entire life is riding
on the results of this exam.
Mash must be under incredible pressure.
I should be encouraging.
Mash, you don't have to worry...
HONK
I wanna go home.
I don't blame you.
Adler, Lang, Orca.
All 12 candidates
from the three dorms are here!
Let's get right to it then!
Elimination's the name of the game!
What better way to do that
than with a survival match!
So we made a dead-or-alive
qualifying exam for you!
It's called, "Deadervant's Haunt"!
The rules are simple!
Find a key hidden somewhere
in this stage and escape!
Huh? That doesn't sound
as dangerous as I thought.
But! The key is in the swim bladder
of a Troll-goosefish!
You must use magic
to pop it like a balloon!
That's really tough. I see.
So that's what this test's about.
Furthermore...
You'll be on the run
from three Deadervants all the while!
WAIL
Monsters!
Yes, monsters.
NEXT EPISODE
MASH BURNEDEAD AND THE BRAWNY BALLOON