Sorry to keep you waiting,
my dear Mash Burnedead.
How splendid.
It's like we're going on a field trip.
Nalcos.
It's heavy like a bowling ball.
What the... Mash can't return the serve!
He'll hit the wall!
Mash!
Surely this isn't the end?
He's gone.
Where did he go?
Spine Magic...
Hell Fall!!
Look!
What?
He's unhurt! How in the world...
Just before slamming into the ground,
Macaron created a sound cushion.
Whoa, I've never heard
of Spine Magic before!
He was able to use magic.
Also, is no one going to call out Mushroom Head
on naming a throw like a magic spell?
More... Let me enjoy this a lot more!
Nalcos.
Nalcos Conte!
Uh-oh! If they hit an attack
at point-blank range...
He stopped it?
What's going on?
It's obvious you're attempting
to guard something.
If you have something to guard,
we cannot fight our utmost.
Go set it aside.
No way. Can this be?
Is this what you call chivalry?
No, this is for my own enjoyment.
A-Amazing!
This is truly a back-and-forth match!
The entire venue is on edge!
What was that useless exchange there?
So freaky. I want
those wasted seconds back.
Neither of them
have gone all out yet.
They're still testing each other.
Macaron's Secondth
would put them a step ahead.
But if both sides go all out,
the match will end in an instant.
Now, I'll have you let me
enjoy all this, Mash Burnedead.
'Kay.
Do show me what you're capable of.
Sounds Fa!
Don't treat it like it's some parlor trick.
My spells are not something
that you can punch to topple.
What now?
In other words, you are most
poorly matched against me.
Sounds Fa!
That's useless.
So one-sided.
So much difference in their personal magic.
I can't block it.
It feels like it comes from within.
This is quite a letdown.
How unfortunate.
It seems you weren't my tartare after all.
Sounds Surround Orchestra!
That's...
...not good!
This is the finale.
Mash!
He didn't stand a chance after all.
That was overwhelming.
Macaron indeed is a true genius.
Macaron didn't even need
to go all out to finish this match.
He disappeared?
What the? They're suddenly buried!
What the hell is going on?
He emerged from underground!?
You can't possibly have done that
so sound doesn't reverberate.
What's going on?
I watched it happen.
Right before being hit with the spell, Mash dug
into the ground and jumped down.
Sound waves oscillate.
But that oscillation decreases
as it meets with obstacles.
So he dampened the sound
by diving underground?
No, sound travels super fast.
Freaky.
Quadriceps Magic...
It can't be...
Guillotine Kick!
- Whoa.
- Sick.
No way.
He took out Macaron in one blow!
Mash Burnedead is such a champ!
Mushroom Head is still claiming
that is really magic?
H-He's on top!?
I didn't think I'd ever see anyone
pinned down in magic school!
I-It's a beatdown!
What a fierce rush
falling down onto Macaron.
I-It's not stopping!
Does he need to go that far?
No. Mash Burnedead understands.
This is what I have been seeking.
I will take you on in my serious form.
Sounds Metamorphosis!
H-Hey, that's...
A child?
You have hair.
To make me look like this...
You really are...
guilty.
They transformed.
So that's...
Margarette Macaron's true form.
They're making the pinky X.
I wonder how Mushroom Head
is doing on the selection exam.
As usual, I'm hot stuff today.
Mr. Ryoh, there's big trouble!
There's a report that Innocent Zero
is on the move again!
Innocent Zero is?
W-We are... Innocent Zero.
That boy belongs to us.
Hands off.
They're after Mushroom Head.
What should we do?
Get security on it immediately.
For now, we'll need Orter and Kaldo
over at Easton to buy us some time.
So, who's on the move?
One of the leaders?
Actually...
it's Innocent Zero himself.
Well, that's really bad.
Um... You've turned into a child.
I haven't simply turned into a child.
This is my form when I unleash
my innate magical power.
I will let you take a good look
at my magic now.
No!
What's this about?
Macaron teleported!
Anyway, is Mash's ear his weakness?
Unleashing magical power also unleashes
more spells I can use.
- Which means, in my current form—
- That's enough.
Huh?
They disappeared?
Over here.
Way over there?
I told you. As my current self,
I am sound itself.
A muscle-type human like me?
Of course not!
What the... They're moving super fast!
Magic that allows them
to travel via sound.
They're literally moving
at the speed of sound.
Trying to catch them without magic means
you have to move faster than sound.
An attack that lands at the same time
when you hear it...
All things considered...
You really are a tough one.
But...
Now I have you.
He's gone?
What the...
How'd he dodge that?
How did you...
He used the properties of sound transfer.
Sound travels faster through liquids
than gases, and even faster through solids.
GAS