The qualifying round of the second
Divine Visionary Candidate Exam.
It is known as "Deadervant's Haunt."
A key is hidden inside a Troll-goosefish
swim bladder somewhere in the stage.
You need to escape by using magic
to pop it like a balloon and obtain the key.
However, you need to do so
while fleeing from three Deadervants.
WAIL
This is impossible!
The upcoming qualifying round
is "Deadervant's Haunt."
Of course, you must pass this
to make it to the main exam!
Rafflesian Mirrors will transmit
everything to the audience!
Cheating will not be accepted!
All entrants, are we ready?
With that, let the match begin!
I want to go home. I just want
to keep sleeping in my bed.
I just gotta find the key, right?
Esepecial!
I should mention the Deadervants are
completely immune to magic! So watch out!
And the moment you touch
one of their axes, it's game over.
You will be transferred out of the stage
with some soul-splitting pain!
One has already been disqualified!
We have 11 candidates left!
ONE DISQUALIFIED
11 SURVIVORS REMAINING
So I have to keep running from
Deadervants and hunt for the key.
No hints about the key's location, either.
Making us scramble blindly
for a key is a pretty poor test.
Unless there's some
unrevealed strategy going on here.
It is a test after all.
Are they trying to see how we
use our magic to escape the enemy?
That's exactly right!
Deadervants are stand-ins
immune to magic.
It's limited to this stage, but powerful magic
made them for that purpose.
When one individual's power
isn't enough to defeat an enemy,
choosing to retreat
is always a valid tactic.
This exam questions how well you do
in a situation where you're forced to flee.
How tasteless! I knew this school
was messed up, but...
One guy out in the first few moments?
This year's candidates are pretty weak.
Well, last year they had Rayne.
There's no comparing these guys.
It's time to run
like your life depends on it!
No way! Deadervant down in one hit!?
It's holding its stomach
and breathing heavily.
This test is about how well you do
when you have to retreat, isn't it?
That Deadervant that I couldn't
do anything against...
He's totally nuts!
Now I just need to find the key.
That's right. A Deadervant is a phantom.
They are not living creatures.
Any damage they take
heals instantly, so be careful!
BA-DUMP
Oh gosh. Then I won't have anything
to do with them anymore.
DAAAAAAAAAAAASH
So, where is this balloon with the key?
Small.
This is going to be rough
with my puny brain.
Huh?
I've gotten smaller.
I casted a spell.
Over here.
It's gone now.
Deadervants have bad eyesight,
but is really sensitive to sound.
You're fine if you keep that in mind.
Dispel.
I'm back to normal.
My personal magic
changes sizes of things at will.
So that's why I shrunk earlier.
You got it.
Thanks for helping me
even though it's an exam.
Oh, come on now.
It's obvious we'll do better
if we work together.
So it's only natural.
In other words,
we have formed an alliance.
Let's clear the exam together.
Huh? This is too sudden.
Then again, you did save me.
You are too nice.
First, the whereabouts of the key.
I'm certain it's somewhere
in the Deadervant's patrol radius.
Huh? Why is that?
This is an exam after all.
I'm sure they're watching for abilities
in spur-of-the-moment situations as well,
but they should have created the field
so that we can logically deduce an answer.
Huh?
No way, did you pass out?
I'm sorry.
It was a bit hard to understand.
Well, in other words...
BAM
We're going to follow Deadervants.
BOOM
Roger.
SHAKE SHAKE SHAKE SHAKE
Where the hell is this key?
Where is it!
Can this be...
TIP TIP
DON'T MAKE A SOUND.
ROGER.
WE'RE SAFE.
SAFE.
HEY, THAT THING...
I knew it.
The key is in the center of the area
a Deadervant moves around in.
That thing under the balloon... a bellows?
So we inflate it until it bursts? Easy.
Huh? Wait, stop! It's obviously...
HOONK
Are you an idiot?
Now we've done it.
You mean you've done it.
That balloon...
Pressing the bellows to inflate it makes a sound
that calls Deadervants to chase you.
My magic can change the size of objects.
So how do we fill it with air?
Why don't we just break the balloon?
All right, I don't see Deadervants.
Now's the time to rip it up.
'Kay.
HONK
Didn't think touching the balloon
would make a sound, too.
Though, I suppose it would.
That means we can't pull the key
out of the balloon, either.
Perhaps if we break that bellows,
the key just falls out.
The key doesn't fall down,
and the balloon doesn't deflate.
Is the key floating inside by magic?
So we do have to inflate
the balloon with magic.
But what kind of magic?
And we already broke the bellows.
Ready.
Bigduk.
Hey! He just used his magic
to make the balloon bigger.
Is he a moron?
What's he gonna do
by making it harder to burst?
By the way, touching the balloon
from the inside also makes a sound,
so you can't crawl inside, either!
Mash.
Huh? What's that?
Is he...
BAM
...about to breakdance!?
Come on, you're joking.
That's impossible!
Seriously impossible.
That's so freaky!
The answer is always simple.
I make the balloon bigger with my magic,
and we send air into the balloon
through the larger air hole.
By breakdancing!
I see.
M-My hat's off to them.
THROB THROB
A living weapon.
He's a living weapon!
There.
We got the first key!
While Mash and Max obtained a key,
in other locations...
Graviole.
I guess I pass this round.
Hey.
Don't attack! Don't punch!
I hate pain! I'm sorry!
Are you all right, Finn?
Dot!
You got your key already?
You're so hopeless.
I'll help you out, then.
Dot, you're bleeding!
You're so hopeless.
No, but blood!
You're so hopeless!
I'm telling you, blood!
Hurray, hurray, hurray.
Well, we somehow made it.
For a while, I was wondering
what would happen.
So, um...
Hm? What is it?
Here.
Huh?
We got this key thanks to you,
so please take it.
You really are a good person.
Huh? That's not really true.
You should take that key.
The exit is that way.
There's a rumor that time
is a factor in your ranking.
Huh? But...
Actually, I heard
all about you from Rayne.
Mr. Rabbits.
I really didn't think you were
this good-natured.
I got the gist of how to obtain the key.
I can do the rest by myself.
Mash, I'm just trying to act tough.
It's my ego saying that I want
to do something for people like you.
So don't worry.
It's an important job for a junior
to keep a senior's honor.
'Kay.
Thank you very much.
Now then...
My bad hunch was right.
Carpaccio Luo-yang of Orca.
Was I able to act like a senior, Rayne?
Bring it on.
Now, candidates who obtained keys
are filing in one after another!
Here are drinks and towels.
Mash!
Dot, Finn.
Balloons and explosive magic
was a good pairing.
That said, you have quite a wound.
I got Finn's key as well.
Are you okay?
I'm surprised you defeated that balloon
without using magic.
Well, I had help so I managed somehow.
But why did he give me the key?
It seems like he had
some reason to do so.
What's wrong?
No, just...
Only nine people
can advance to the next stage!
Who will take that final spot?
There he...
And there you have it!
The last one is...
Orca dorm's Carpaccio Luo-yang!
But this is quite horrible.
There's so much blood.
Was there a need to hurt him this badly?
Could this be a declaration of war!?
I don't need weaklings.
Weaklings are useless.
So it shouldn't matter
what I do to them.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
If you go any further, I'll punch you.
More like, did you really
have to go that far?
I just said it.
I can do whatever I want.
Carpaccio Luo-yang.
The top continuing student for this year.
Just like Lance, he's a true elite.
H-Here's your drink and towel.
Weaklings should keep quiet.
SLUP SUP SUP SUP
Can that be...
PHEW
Sorry. It's 3 o'clock, which is when I like
to take my homemade special muscle drink.
It's a protein shake!
Powdered beans.
It makes it easier to absorb protein.
The nerve of making a protein shake with
the water that was about to go on his head. Scary.
Sorry, but a schedule for protein
consumption is very important.
Also, you keep calling people "weaklings."
But I have yet to meet
anyone stronger than me.
Besides, the definition of strength
differs from person to person.
Wait.
HONK
What does it mean to be strong?
He brought up the topic,
but he confused himself.
Hold it right there!
Save the fighting for the examination!
Is that understood!?
Without further ado,
let's move on to the next exam!
Our robes changed colors?
Here's your next exam!
It's called "The Life Crystal."
This will be a team battle!
Each team has three members.
With nine candidates,
we will have three teams!
After the teams are set, the three members
will get one crystal each.
And you will go break the crystals
of opposing teams!
A team is disqualified
when all their crystals are broken!
I see.
So that's why it's a team match.
Yo! Your explanation's too complicated
and our captain's brain isn't keeping up!
Make it easier to understand, damn it!
W-Well, in other words, you split up
into teams and break each other's crystals.
So we just smash everyone
else's crystals. That's easy!
Mash, smash crystal. Mash, smash crystal.
That's right! Smash! Smash 'em!
Smash crystal.
Moreover...
Lance is in a different team.
What should we do?
Now we will hand out the crystals.
These crystals are fragile,
so handle them carefully!
These crystals determine the exam results,
and therefore our fate.
Each team has three members.
If all our crystals break, we drop out.
So even if mine breaks, at least...
It slipped.
W-We're still fine. Dot's crystal...
This thing was so slippery.
GLOOM
HEART TEAM'S (TWO) CRYSTALS
LIFESPAN
23 SECONDS
Bad, bad, very bad!
This means that it's all over
if my crystal breaks.
Oh, don't worry.
We'll make sure to protect
your crystal through all of this.
You guys.
That's right. As long as
these two are at my side.
Wait, why are you looking so smug?
You should show some remorse.
Everyone, sorry for the wait!
Time to begin the exam!
Stage shift!
Just like the previous round, candidates
will be scattered throughout the stage!
Which team will protect their crystals
to the end and pass this exam!?
ALONE...
I-It's a team match,
so why are we forced to split apart!?
Damn it!
He was all alone.
NEXT EPISODE
FINN AMES AND THE FRIEND