Mr. Wahlberg.
Why did you call for all of us?
Hiding the fact he's a Lackmagic and attending
Easton Academy is out of the question.
There's no need for an inquiry.
We need to abide by the rules
and give this boy the maximum penalty.
Divine Visionaries, might I ask you
to defer his sentencing?
This is the first time
Innocent Zero sent a messenger.
There is a high chance this boy
will give us a lead on them.
We can't afford
to lose him at this juncture.
Huh? The headmaster
seems really important.
You know...
Mr. Wahlberg is a previous Divine Visionary.
He's a living legend, the only one to go
toe-to-toe against Innocent Zero in his youth.
And the only one that I,
the next top dog of the world, respect.
He's a man among magic users.
Listen closely.
'Kay.
Mr. Wahlberg, I understand your position.
But I cannot accept it.
Regulations exist to maintain order.
Lackmagic should be purged.
That's just the way...
Mr. Wahlberg, please!
It's true. He cannot use magic.
He's a bit rough around the edges
and not too scholarly.
However, he has an unusual gift
to sway people's hearts.
I believe that people like him will change
how we perceive this world.
Of course, that is not all.
Until now, those without magic
have been treated as inferior.
But I take some issue
with that unjust treatment.
Our values change alongside history.
However, redefining our values
takes courage
as we must admit
our injustices thus far.
That said...
What is wrong is still wrong.
Mr. Wahlberg.
I respect your position, but ignoring rules
and forcing your opinion...
I ask of you as well.
Rayne, even you?
I do agree with the headmaster's opinion,
but Mash Burnedead has also
proven himself worthy of our trust.
Including my trust.
So you like rabbits?
No, not that.
Rayne, I know what you're getting at.
But sentimental opinions
shouldn't change regulations.
What a pain. Follow the book
and get this over with.
Mr. Wahlberg, you are quite right to say so.
But the public won't allow
such an exception.
There's nothing to reconsider.
Lackmagics need to be purged.
You're letting emotions
take priority over rational thought.
My thoughts align with yours.
Our magical power
is a special gift from God.
It's natural for those without it
to be excluded.
That's because they aren't the same as us.
However, one Lackmagic
just saved my life.
I know that
I should be following regulations.
If I am being remiss in my duties, so be it.
But this case was mine to process.
I would like you to defer
his sentencing if possible.
You may punish me as you see fit.
But I will not change my verdict.
Only under these conditions.
He will act only under our supervision
as a pawn against Innocent Zero.
And he must prove he's strong enough
to fight Innocent Zero.
That proof is to become this year's
Divine Visionary candidate.
Should you fail,
you will be purged immediately.
After all, it's only a deferment.
All right. Understood.
But to embody the headmaster's wishes
and for me to live in peace with everyone...
That alone won't be enough.
I will beat Innocent Gyro up.
With my fist.
And that's what happened.
Innocent Zero.
You have to go against
such a dangerous organization?
So you can't use magic?
Nope.
Trying to win against me without magic?
You really couldn't use magic.
Nope.
Gotcha. Then let's go out and have fun.
Wait, what now?
A sudden suggestion to go have fun.
Maybe Dot was worried about Mash.
They did defer the sentencing,
so this is probably better than sulking.
But I wonder what kind of street clothes
everyone will wear.
Here I am!
KAKLANG
Full-plate armor!?
I mean, fun is basically a battle.
What the heck does that mean?
I'm here now.
That must be Mash.
RLL RLL
He's in full workout mode!
I've never gone out with friends before,
so I wasn't sure what to wear.
But did you really need that ab wheel?
My goodness.
I really don't want to be seen
with these two.
Sorry I'm late.
I'm glad Lance is in normal...
LITTLE SISTER LOVE
- Love.
- Cringe!
Did she just wink? And talk!?
Yeah, come at me from anywhere!
Dear sister, you're cute today, too.
This group is just so detestable!
There's a famous game you can play
only here in Marchétte Street.
See, over there.
TICKLE TICKLE
A tickle koala's snot hardens, so we play darts
by tickling its nose and making it sneeze.
Oh! Sounds like fun.
I'll try it.
TICKLE TICKLE
Well, it's hard for novices
to even hit the target.
THUNK
Sorry, Dot.
Well, it's your first time.
I'll show you how it's done.
TICKLE TICKLE
THUNK
A flying arm bar?
- All right! Fight's on, damn it!
- Let's go.
- Okay.
A new wand?
Yeah. I've been wanting
to try out a new wand.
And lately, there are rumors that
the Divine Visionary Candidate Exam is near.
Because of the Innocent Zero case,
the exam will be held earlier this year.
But that works in our favor.
Based on the coin count,
we're sure to be taking the selection exam.
If we can pass that, the only thing left
is the final screening.
Even though you can't use magic...
For my sister's sake,
I'm not going to go easy on you.
We're here.
This is the place.
Welcome.
Easton kids, are ye?
Oh, yes.
So many different kinds.
The wand shop is always nothing but hype!
Maybe I should replace my wand, too.
Wowee.
Your magical power
summons a fitting wand.
Wands are tools for releasing magical power.
Basically extensions
of the magic users' bodies.
A fitting wand can drastically improve
your magic too.
I think my magical power went up
because of my classes thanks to my wand.
That's why you need to periodically
gauge your magic and...
It's better to choose a wand
that fits your current self.
Impressive.
Even among wands for double-liners,
that one is quite the item.
Amazing.
I don't like it!
You're not gauging?
Huh?
Oh, no! Mash lacks magical power,
so no wand would react to him.
Then, I guess...
You're doing it?
What's that wand? The one on the floor.
RTTL RTTL RTTL
Huh? Scary. What the...
Oh, that? We've had that wand here
in this shop for ages.
It's so heavy that nobody can ever lift it.
It's said that elf water
springs up from beneath it,
and magnificent wands
can be crafted using that water.
But it's no more than a legend.
No amount of muscle or magic has been able
to lift it for the past millennium.
That's bad, old man!
Saying that to him would...
You don't get it at all!
What do you mean?
H-Hey, what are you...
Then, I'll take this one.
Thank you so much.
That wand is all yours.
Yay.
Freaky.
In the end, Lance didn't buy a wand.
I'm sorry, my chores
took longer than expected!
I had some bamboo-siness to do!
Lemon. Captain.
All right! We're gonna play!
We're living our best student lives!
That was fun.
I've never gone out with friends before.
Let's come back again sometime.
- Yup.
- Damn straight!
Let's come again!
Next time with my sister, too.
Buh-Buh-Bamboo!
And several days passed.
Gold coin count, one, two, three...
Seven.
Preparation for the selection exam
is as good as done.
It's finally time.
But first...
You're going to visit home?
Now? Right before the selection exam?
Are you serious?
I'm sorry. I-I-I will stay.
Well, I think I'll go back home.
Wait, what was that flashback just now?
Someone lacking magic
wants to be a Divine Visionary.
This is unprecedented.
Headmaster Wahlberg is getting on in years.
He can no longer make rational decisions.
Those in power have a responsibility
to stop disturbances before they arise.
So, I have to do something about this.
Let me be clear.
See that he cannot participate
in the Divine Visionary Candidate Exam.
Orca dorm prefect, Margarette Macaron.
Ortie, it's unusual
that you'd ask me for a favor.
But you know I don't march
to the beat of just anyone's drum.
I only care about one thing.
Stimulation.
There should be no lack of that.
Mash Burnedead
bested Lang's prefect, Abel.
Abel the coin seeker, you say?
Hmph, that's not bad.
But simply hoarding coins
doesn't measure stren—
He did it without magic.
Leave the cleanup to me.
Go wild.
Spring has arrived.
So creepy.
Oh, Mash!
I'm glad you made it back here, Mash!
I'm somehow surviving.
You hanging in there?
Y-Yes. E-Easy peasy.
R-Really?
Excuse us!
Huh? No way.
You can't be...
What? Mash's friends?
I'm so touched.
To think Mash has made friends...
Because I wasn't able to expose him
to the outside world,
I didn't think this day would come.
We're not such superficial things like friends.
Huh?
You use the word "rival"
and read it as "buddy."
Though, I'm tougher than him.
He's even got a rival.
Father-in-law, it's nice to meet you.
I give my regards for the future.
I am Mash's future wife.
Even a fiancée!?
We haven't even held hands,
so rest assured.
Please be at ease.
Mash is doing well at school.
This isn't much,
but please have some herbal tea.
Oh, thank you.
That's so not like you.
I have something for you, too.
- Please have some merch.
- Of who?
My little sister.
Why!?
He doesn't understand that everyone
has different priorities.
I-I see.
They're quite unique. All of them.
Yes, they are.
You must have a hard time.
Yes.
But...
I was never able to let Mash
go outside until now.
I never dreamed he'd be surrounded
by such wonderful friends.
I hope it lasts forever.
I'm sure...
I'm sure it will.
Hope they won't mind us barging in.
To defeat Abel
so soundly without magic.
You think I can let
someone like that slide?
Hey, what was that boy's name?
Mash.
It's Mash Burnedead.
Right, right. Mash Burnedea—
Dear me.
You're playing his bodyguard now?
I just happened to pass by.
I heard a nasty-sounding laughter over here.
Well, well. If it isn't the Sword Cane...
Divine Visionary, Rayne Ames.
Orca prefect Margarette Macaron's evil hands
approach by Orter Madl's order.
But Mash is still oblivious of it.
All right, let's play a board game!
Yeah!
He really didn't know.
NEXT EPISODE
RAYNE AMES AND GOD'S GIFT