During the final round of
the Divine Visionary Candidate Exam,
Innocent Zero suddenly invaded.
Headmaster Wahlberg and Innocent Zero
took to the skies and confronted each other.
On ground, where time has stopped
due to magic,
Mash was punching Innocent Zero's
core member, Cell, with his fist.
I remember now.
You're the black thorny guy.
But I've seen it once before.
So, the same thing twice? Please.
Mash forgets the face
of someone he's fought before,
but apparently he doesn't forget magic,
even if he's seen it just once.
Adam Jobs.
The legendary magic user
blessed with overwhelming magical ability
who reigned at the top
of the Magic Realm for several centuries.
He systemized magic theory on his own,
and created an educational system.
Furthermore, he created the Bureau of Magic
as an administrative organization.
His vast influence
was felt by the magical society.
However, most of his effort
in his later years
went into social assistance to those
who were unable to use magic.
Noblesse Oblige.
The strong exist for the weak.
He entrusted his ideals to his three pupils,
including Wahlberg.
And now...
Master.
I finally acquired it.
The magic to restore life
from fragments of flesh.
Though, it only restores time
elapsed on the body.
I can't bring the psyche back with it.
How could you...
From here...
I, Necross Mance,
will be your opponent.
Marionettes are my specialty.
I will make sure to satisfy you.
All of you...
How far do you intend to push me?
My oh my, are you going to attack?
Though a puppet, this is a great man
you once hailed as master.
Th-This magical power...
Despite living such a long life, our master
couldn't fight his lifespan
and became decrepit.
However, I restored
Master's body in prime form.
His magical power was the greatest in history.
I recall Master was so very fond of you.
So, isn't this a wonderful reunion?
Noblesse Oblige, you say?
That's right.
Those of high standing have the responsibility
and duty to guide the weak.
To me, that's a phrase that people who
neglect effort use to protect themselves.
There is some truth there, Wahlberg.
There's no purpose in our
giving of ourselves for others.
Now hold on a second, you dummy!
Don't refute your own master!
You really want to assert dominance?
No.
I tease. Just kidding, sorry.
Well, the fact that you can come up
with opinions like that
simply means that you're still quite young!
Well, you'll figure it out someday.
Because you're strong.
That got repelled!?
Master was the greatest man I knew.
However, the times have changed.
What's important is not the past,
but the present.
If you would descend
the present into chaos,
I won't show mercy,
even against my master.
Because my present form
is the strongest, Master.
Wahlberg.
Wahlberg Baigan.
The man who used to rule
this realm as a Divine Visionary,
and the one who continues to stand
at the top of the Magic Realm to this day.
His skills are assuredly
the strongest in the realm.
However! That's just
in the present Magic Realm.
Dark Impact!
Adam Jobs' dark magic
returns everything to the void.
It covers everything in darkness.
You shall be enveloped by darkness.
Dark Snake!
This magical power...
Truly is from his prime.
The great power Adam Jobs used
to control the Magic Realm with...
Dark magic.
It's magic that sends
anything it touches to the void.
It even sends
an opponent's magic into the void.
Which means, once cast, dark magic
cannot be repelled by other magic.
Wahlberg didn't counter against Dark Snake
because he knew his magic wouldn't work.
It's dark magic that his master once used.
There's no way he's oblivious
to its characteristics.
This toy is the best yet!
It has the best specs
of any that I've dealt with!
I will continue to use it
preciously as one of my own.
Dark Snake Double!
He cut out the dark magic!?
Dark Impact!
Arm!
My arm!
What? Don't worry.
My magic controls space.
The body part you lost just went to
a slightly distant spot. It won't kill you.
I-I see.
Just like how you sliced my body,
space and all.
You carved out the entire space that the dark magic
was occupying in order to deal with it.
Then, I will hit you with enough dark magic
so you can't cut it all out.
Dark Impact Absol!
It's impossible
to overcome dark magic.
Even Wahlberg won't have enough time
to cut out space with this many!
No way.
He carved out such a wide range
of this ridiculous magic!
I'm using the man who once
took the Magic Realm by storm.
Even if he's the toughest now, there can't be
this large of a gap in skill.
Furthermore, I'm using dark magic.
It's magic that stands
at the pinnacle of all magic!
Dark Tremendos!
Dark magic at full throttle!
In a clash of two spells, there's no way
dark magic would ever lose!
It seems you have a misunderstanding.
Everything till now has been
the abilities of the wand itself.
This is what casting a spell is like,
young one.
What is this magical power?
Space Sacrifice!
S-Stay away! Stay away!
Stay away!
Well, you'll figure it out someday.
Because you're strong.
Master, I will inherit all of your teachings.
So please, rest in peace, once again.
You still not know of decline, Wahlberg.
It's your turn next, right, Innocent Zero?
Explomb!
Graviole!
This again, damn it!?
There's so many.
They're trying to deplete our magical power.
Quit your whining.
It's a calm analysis of the situation.
I'd like to assist Mushroom Head,
but if we leave here,
danger befalls the students.
So magic you've seen once
doesn't work on you?
- So, uh...
- Huh?
Why am I being targeted to begin with?
Do you know the Forbidden Magic
of Body Construction?
Forbidden Magic of Body Construction?
Forbidden Magic of Body Construction.
Dark magic used to create an immortal heart
from the hearts of six blood relatives.
That is why Father prepared six children
as vessels to nurture the hearts.
In short, you are a creation of Father's.
You are merely a part built
to create Father's perfect body.
SHOCK
Shock!
Rejoice. This is quite honorable.
You will become a part
of the being closest to God.
Basically, it's like how you need protein
to create better muscles?
So that's the kind of existence I am.
What the hell is he talking about?
Man.
HONK
That's heavy.
It's quite heavy. My life, that is.
For now, I'll take a nap.
He fell asleep in seconds.
Hey, don't sleep!
No good. I woke up,
but it's still reality, apparently.
By the way, are you one of my brothers?
I am not.
I am merely a clone created
by giving Father's blood to a corpse.
I was born so my life can be used
for Father's grand scheme.
I see.
As a son, becoming a part of
Father's body is the greatest honor.
Yet, one turned out to be trash like you.
I am so infuriated,
I can't calm myself down.
Your life is worthless anyway.
Aren't you glad it has some use?
So with my own hands,
I'll slash you until...
Damn him, I'm still talking!
Heavy life or not, worthless life or not,
it doesn't matter.
I'm unstoppable, so gimme your best.
I can't let him set the pace.
He was created by Father, so I can
understand that he has some power.
Then...
I will go full throttle from the start.
Come on.
Summon Hephaestus.
The heck is that?
This is the wand's full power unleashed.
Its true form!
Whoa.
Magic can evolve in countless ways.
It's based on the user's
total magical power.
The hell is that?
This immense magical power...
Father only seeks your heart.
I will slice everything else apart.
Diamond Cutter!
That was close.
My place of learning.
These discs are diamond tipped.
There's nothing in this world
they can't cut.
Furthermore, the discs will hunt you down
until they cut you to ribbons.
I have to ignore the discs
and go directly after him.
I see. Two out of four are on standby
to keep me away from him.
Dangerous! Four of them
is absolutely dangerous!
What's wrong? Are you chickening out?
But if you flee,
I will clear out all the humans
in this area as punishment.
Black Diamond!
Something else popped up.
A wand unleashing its
true power via a summon spell
not only has enhanced abilities,
but the amount of magical power unleashed
goes up several orders of magnitude.
These 1000 diamonds will pierce
those rubbish bodies at this academy.
This tawdry place where you mistakenly
believe was a new home for you,
and all your useless followers
will die.
Give up already, Mash Burnedead!
He's leaving?
What's the meaning of this?
Is he leaving
the students behind and fleeing?
Did he give up,
unable to come up with an attack?
Did he abandon all his friends
who are fighting?
I did a loop around the academy
to shake them all off.
No way.
He shook off all of the discs chasing him?
What kind of speed does he run at?
And he's clinging onto me
so he can take me down with him
when the discs come.
But what a shame.
Did you forget I had this?
You can't break through my diamond skin
with physical blows!
I will slice you apart!
Die!
So this is all you can do?
You're trash!
What a pathetic sight!
Just you wait, I'll slice your buddies
in half so they can follow after...
Th-This texture.
A cream puff?
What in the world...
Cream Puff Party.
- I thought I killed you!
- Cream Puff Party.
Cream Puff Party.
What is the meaning of this...
Why are you alive?
Cream Puff Party.
Stop it! The custard is going up my nose!
I can't...
Cream Puff Party.
I-I can't breathe.
Can't... breathe...
Biceps Magic.
Python Choke.
Hypoxia.
When the brain is deprived of oxygen,
it half-enters hallucinations.
Right before the disc hit,
Mash took the remaining time and
the hardness of diamond into account,
and gave up physical attacks.
And immediately used explosive contraction of
his biceps to put pressure on the carotid artery
to cut off the oxygen supply.
As a result, he KO'ed his foe
in less than a second.
Of course, that includes the Black Diamond.
I care a lot about this school.
If you're claiming to destroy it,
I'll choke you out as many times
as I need to...
with my muscles.
NEXT EPISODE
WAHLBERG BAIGAN AND THE GREATEST DANGER